

KISHORE KUMAR

Production Manager

Contact Me

- 9345134186
- kishore.kv2107@gmail.c om
 - Saravana Nagar,
- Koundanpalayam Coimbatore,India



Social Profile



linkedin.com/in/kishore -kumar-63068422b

Other Info

Skills

ISO documentation, PPAP, APQP, 5S,7QC tools, KAIZEN, FMEA, AutoCAD Drafting, MS Office, routine production documentation.

Awards

Best quality adjustor in 2008 for best elevator ride comfort and quality of installation (KONE)



About Me

Production incharge with 14 years of experience in rubber industries. Duties I took in responsibility were supervising the everyday operations of productions and perform duties such as overseeing staff, evaluating the production effectiveness, increasing community awareness between teams, supporting organization goals, developing plans, organizing events, supporting new plant installation and tracking budgets. Thereby contributing my share of efforts towards the achievement of the goals, profits and

growth of the enterprise and to build up a career along with them.



Experience

2006 - 2009

KONE

Elevator

India Pvt.

Ltd, Mumbai | Quality Adjustor

Quality Control & Installation of New Elevators

2010 - 2012 **T**

TVS Rubber Factory, Madurai | Executive - New Product Development

New product development & production control of automobile rubber products.

Best employee for production norms increasing in rubber sheet bias cutting process (JK Fenner)

Languages

English, Hindi, Tamil

Interest

Music, Travelling

2012 - 2015 JK Fenner India Pvt Ltd | Assistant Officer

Production, planning and control of power transmission cogged &

V belts.ISO

documents(PPAP,FMEA,APQP)

2015 - 2022 James Walker Inmarco Industries Pvt Ltd | Works Manager

Production manager for industrial rubber bellows and auto ancillary rubber products.

Product Developments, ISO Documentation, employee recruitment and welfare activities.



Education

2003 - 2006 V.S.V.N.

Poly technic

college | D.M.E (Mechanical Engineering)

Passed with First Class with honours (83.96%)



Projects

2008 - 2009 KONE Elevators India Pvt Ltd | Scaffoldless Erection

G+49 floors elevator installation was done by scaffoldless erection method. (Speed of 3.5m/sec)

2011 - 2012 TVS Rubber Factory | Product Development Achievement

Implementing auto releasing concepts in bellow dust cover products.

Implementing mechanized shearing tool deflashing for rubber products.

2013 - 2014 JK Fenner India Pvt Ltd | SCADA Improvements

Implementation of Vacuum pressure monitoring in SCADA historical graph.

Improvement of auto cycle in pot curing process to avoid sleeve rejection with SCADA.

2020 - 2021 James Walker Inmarco Industries Pvt Ltd | Industrial Rubber Bellows Development

Industrial rubber bellows product Developments, it's equipments purchased and installation

Kishore Kumar